evs-translations.com 2014-06-17

# Professional interpreting and translation services | EVS Translations

This privacy policy sets out what information EVS Translations collects when you visit this website and how this is used and protected. 

EVS Translations is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide specific information, we will only use this in accordance with this privacy policy. 

EVS Translations reserves the right to update this policy as and when required. For this reason, we recommend that you check this page from time to time in order to keep up-to-date with any changes. This policy is effective from August 5 2008 and was last amended on February 18 2010. 

## COLLECTION OF PERSONAL DATA

We only collect personal data when you request an online translation quote or references or when you apply online as a freelance translator. This data is collected insofar as you choose to share this with us. 

## PROCESSING AND USE OF PERSONAL DATA

EVS Translations uses the collected data in order to better understand your needs and to optimize the range of services which we can provide you with, and in particular for the following reasons where applicable:

  * Internal record keeping
  * Improving our products and services
  * Customising our website according to the needs of our customers.
  * Sending promotional emails (using the email address which you have provided) containing information about new products, special offers and any other information which we think you may find interesting, provided that you have explicitly given your consent for us to do this – usually when making an initial online request for information, services or references.

You have the right to withdraw your future consent at any time by simply sending us an email: dataprotection(at)evs-translations.com 

## USE OF COOKIES

Cookies are small files which ask permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies help to analyse web traffic and allow the server to identify when a user is visiting a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to users as individuals. The web application can tailor its functions to the needs, likes and dislikes of these users by gathering and saving information about their preferences. 

EVS Translations uses cookies to identify which pages are accessed. Using this data, we can analyse traffic on our website in order to tailor its configuration to the needs of our customers. We use this data for statistical analysis purposes only and then delete it from the system. 

Cookies help us to provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers accept cookies automatically, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. However, this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

## LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our website may contain links to other websites. However, once you have used one of these links to leave our website, please note that we do not have any control over other websites. Therefore, we accept no responsibility for the protection of information that you may provide when visiting such websites. The websites of other providers are not covered by this privacy policy. Please exercise caution when visiting these websites and check the privacy policy applicable to the site in question. 

Please inform us if you believe that the linked websites contravene the applicable law or contain questionable content. 

## SECURITY

EVS Translations takes all the technical and organisational measures necessary for the protection of your personal information against loss or misuse. We will not sell, distribute or pass on your personal information to third parties unless we are required to do so by law. 

## RIGHT TO INFORMATION

We will be happy to inform you of any personal data which we have saved regarding you specifically. 

## CONTACT

If you have any questions regarding your personal data, please do not hesitate to contact our data protection officer in confidence: dataprotection(at)evs-translations.com
